Serhat Ismail Zunluoglu

Jr. Front-End Developer

Nationality: Turkish Adress: Gebze/Kocaeli Driver License: B

Mail: serhatismail12@gmail.com

Social Media: https://linktr.ee/serhatzunluoglu Github: https://github.com/serhatzunluoglu

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/serhatzunluoglu



SUMMARY

Hello, I am Serhat İsmail Zunluoğlu, I am studying in the 4th year of Computer Engineering Department at Necmettin Erbakan University. I am trying to improve myself in the front-end field. I am interested in Html, CSS, Boostrap, Javascript and React and I'm trying to learn these technologies. I try to develop myself and gain experience by participating in communities and taking an active role in clubs.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering Aug 2020 - Present Necmettin Erbakan University, Konya/Turkiye

EXPERIENCE

Jr.Front-End Developer Oct 2023 – Present *Invivo Software and Technology Inc.*

I work part-time as a remote jr.front end developer in this startup and we work with technologies such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, SCSS and React.

Intern UI Developer Aug 2023 – Sep 2023 Jotform

I was one of the 4 trainees who formed the jr.phoenix team under the phoenix team at jotform company. I am working as a UI Developer Intern in this team.

Head of R&D Department and Apr 2022 - Present Supervisory Board Mirketgiller

We are a Mirketgiller family where we will voluntarily organize events and webinars and interact with each other. I work here as the head of the research and development department.

Yurt-Time Sports Student Nov 2022 – Feb 2023 Ministry of Youth and Sports

Within the scope of the Yurt Time Sports Project in KYK Seydişehir dormitory, we have done the work of the dormitory officers regarding the students, such as permitting, entry-exit procedures, and creating events and activities.

Intern Aug 2022 – Aug 2022 Akım Metal R&D Center

At Akım Metal R&D Center Software Team, I first reinforced my knowledge about HTML and CSS. Then I tried to learn Javascript and Angular's structure.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Social Assistant Mar 2023 - Present *Kodluyoruz*

I am a volunteer at Kodluyoruz. We organize trainings and game events on discord in long bootcamps.

Core Team Organizer Mar 2023 - Present Google Developers Student Clubs NEU I am Core Team Organizer of Google Developers Students Club Necmettin Erbakan University.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Programming Languages JavaScript, Python, C++

Tools, Technologies, Libraries and Frameworks React, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS

Npm, Git & GitHub & GitLab

HARD & SOFT SKILLS

Software's

Visual Studio Code, ChatGPT, ClickUp

Soft Skills

Teamwork, Communication, Problem-solving, Leadership, Creativity, Agile Methodologies, Friendly

LANGUAGES

Turkish Native
English Professional Working Competence

CERTIFICATES AND COURSES

My All Certificates

Click Here

Software Factory | React.Js Apr 2023

Üretken Akademi

Hi-Code Front-End Workshop May 2022 *Kodluyoruz*

PROJECTS

Software Factory Projects Mar 2023 Projects I do on a weekly basis in the software factory program. <u>Click Here</u>